# BRADLEY YARROW

Software Developer

#### Contact

**Address** 

Lagos, Lagos, 23401

**Phone** 

2348118022308

E-mail

yarrowbradley@gmail.com

LinkedIn

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bradley-yarrow

#### **Skills**

Laravel

Vuejs

PHP

**Javascript** 

Testing – PHPUnit , Laravel Dusk

Self-driven and fast learner

Highly adaptable to different work environments

Technical Analysis

Excellent Problem Solving
Skills

Software Best Practices

An Enthusiastic Software Developer with over 4 years of experience eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Clear understanding of software development. Motivated to learn, grow and excel.

# **Work History**

2019-09 -Current

### **Backend Engineer**

PEEXOO TECHNOLOGIES, Lekki, Lagos

- Participate on development process of backend application which has over 5000 active users using Larayel.
- Create RESTFUL API for different parts of Application using Laravel.
- Manage servers including dev operations on AWS.
- Collaborate with team members to ensure application api is well tested and documented.
- Improve on speed of application as data and users grow.
- Built Findmyface and lookalike API with Amazon Rekognition and got over 10000 users.
- Improved performance and reliability of databases, web services and other integrations.
- Deployed cloud infrastructure and distributed systems on AWS.
- Developed and maintained core product services, libraries and frameworks.

2020-03 -2021-02

# **Software Engineer**

Decisive Technologies, Lekki, Lagos

- Added features to Dinerr Web application API
- Worked on both Frontend part of application and also backend part of application with over 5000 users.
- Built and Embeddable widget with Vuejs for businesses with over 50 restaurants using it.
- Created unique link so customers can purchase meals without signing in.
- Participated in project planning and reviews.
- Setup server architecture and worked as DevOps person using AWS

Data Storage and Caching
– MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

Cloud Services and Hosting -AWS, Digital Ocean , Netlify

Algorithm implementation

Agile Workflow

**Troubleshooting** 

- Created procedures for system monitoring, recovery, backup and optimization.
- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

2019-03 -2019-10

#### Web Developer

Nextpayday, Port Harcourt, Rivers State

- Added features to Nextpayday loan application using Laravel.
- Worked on both Frontend and backend part of Laravel application.
- Added loan repayment features and other features too.
- Made sure investors on loan platform could properly interact with platform without issues.

2018-04 -2019-09

# Web Developer

Gerocare, Lekki, Lagos

- Added Features to Existing Laravel Application with over 10000 users
- Implementation of new Ideas from The companies
   CTO
- Created a third party API for other Medical applications to use the Doctors information's available on the platform

2017-04 -2017-08

# **Web Developer Intern**

Hostnownow Limited, Lekki, Lagos

- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers, and operating systems.
- Studied user requirements and implemented requirements into solutions.
- Assisted with development of software user manuals.

# **Education**

2008-01 -2014-07

#### **High School Degree**

Macdonald Memorial International Institute - Nigeria

# **Interests**

Gaming

Scrabble